<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SAFENEST</string>
    <string name="label">HEALTHY MOMS, STRONG BABIES</string>
    <string name="select_language_hint">Language</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Please enter your name so that we know how to contact you.</string>
    <string name="label_gestational">You need to calculate the gestational age and estimated due date
    for the application to work correctly.</string>
    <string name="enter_first">Enter the first day of your last period.</string>
    <string name="estimated_dueDate">If you know the Estimated Due Date, you may enter it below:</string>

    <string name="sixweek">Congratulations on reaching this milestone!
        You might be experiencing common symptoms like implantation bleeding (light spotting), fatigue, breast tenderness,
        and the onset of nausea and vomiting (morning sickness).</string>


    <string name="week2">
        At the start of this week, you ovulate. Your egg is fertilized 12 to
        24 hours later if a sperm penetrates it. Over the next several
        days, the fertilized egg will start dividing into multiple cells as it
        travels down the fallopian tube, enters your uterus, and starts to
        burrow into the uterine lining. \n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 2nd week: \n\n
        Ovulation:\n
        \t\t• Egg development: An egg starts maturing in one of your \n\t\t\t ovaries, inside a fluid-filled sac called a follicle.
        \n\t\t• Hormonal changes: Levels of estrogen and \n\t\t\t follicle-stimulating
        hormone (FSH) increase, stimulating the \n\t\t\t egg\'s growth.
        \n\t\t• Ovulation event: Around day 14 (can vary depending on your
        \n\t\t\t cycle), the mature egg ruptures from the follicle and is
        \n\t\t\t released into the fallopian tube, ready for fertilization.

        \n\nPossible symptoms you might experience:\n
       \t\t• Mittelschmerz: A mild pain or twinge in your lower abdomen \n\t\t\t on one side, indicating ovulation.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus changes: Mucus becomes thinner and \n\t\t\t clearer,
        more receptive to sperm.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Consult with a healthcare professional if you have any
        \n\t\t\t questions or concerns about your menstrual cycle or
        \n\t\t\t conception.
       \n\t\t• Accurate pregnancy dating starts from the first day of your
        \n\t\t\t last menstrual period, not week 2.
    </string>

    <string name="week3">
        Now nestled in the nutrient-rich lining of your uterus is a
        microscopic ball of hundreds of rapidly multiplying cells that will
        develop into your baby. This ball of cells, called a blastocyst, has
        begun to produce the pregnancy hormone hCG, which tells your
        ovaries to stop releasing eggs\n\nHere\'s what happens during the 3rd week: \n
        \n\t\t• Implantation: This is the star of the show! By week 3, the
        \n\t\t\t fertilized egg, now called a blastocyst, has traveled down
        \n\t\t\t your fallopian tube and burrows itself into the lining of your
        \n\t\t\t uterus. This process usually takes about 6-10 days after
        \n\t\t\t ovulation

        \n\t\t• Early cell differentiation: The blastocyst starts to \n\t\t\t differentiate
        into two groups of cells: the inner cell mass \n\t\t\t (which will
        eventually become your baby) and the outer layer \n\t\t\t (which will
        form the placenta and other supportive \n\t\t\t structures).

        \n\t\t• Placenta formation: The outer layer of the blastocyst begins
        \n\t\t\t to develop into the placenta, a vital organ that will nourish
        \n\t\t\t your baby and remove waste products throughout \n\t\t\t pregnancy.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Implantation bleeding: Some women experience light
        \n\t\t\t spotting or bleeding around the time of implantation, which
        \n\t\t\t can be mistaken for a period. This is usually nothing to worry
        \n\t\t\t about, but if you have any concerns, consult your doctor.

        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness: Rising hormone levels can make your
        \n\t\t\t breasts feel swollen and tender.

        \n\t\t• Fatigue: You might feel more tired than usual due to
        \n\t\t\t hormonal changes and the body\'s increased energy \n\t\t\t demands.

        \n\t\t• Food cravings or aversions: Some women experience \n\t\t\t changes
        in their sense of taste and smell, leading to cravings \n\t\t\t for
        certain foods or aversions to others.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: It\'s important to remember that not everyone
        \n\t\t\t experiences pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and \n\t\t\t some
        women might not feel anything at all in the early \n\t\t\t weeks.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Prenatal vitamin: Start taking a prenatal vitamin that \n\t\t\t contains
        folic acid and other essential nutrients to support \n\t\t\t your baby\'s development.
        \n\t\t•Healthy lifestyle: Focus on eating a balanced diet, getting
        \n\t\t\t regular exercise, and staying hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Doctor\'s visit: Schedule a prenatal appointment with your
        \n\t\t\t doctor to discuss your pregnancy and any concerns you \n\t\t\t have.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Weight gain: You likely won\'t experience any significant \n\t\t\t weight gain in the third week.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: If you\'ve been tracking your basal \n\t\t\t body temperature, it should remain elevated after ovulation.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: Your cervical mucus might become thicker \n\t\t\t and creamier as your body prepares for implantation.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and the experiences mentioned \n\t\t\t above are just general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• If you have any concerns or questions, don\'t hesitate to \n\t\t\t talk to your doctor
    </string>

    <string name="week4">
        Your ball of cells is now officially an embryo.
        You\'re now about 4 weeks from the beginning of your last period.
        It\'s around this time– when your next period would normally be due –
        that you might be able to get a positive result on a home pregnancy test\n
        \nYour baby is the size of a poppy seed\n\nHere\'s what happens during the 4th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Rapid cell division: The inner cell mass from the blastocyst
        \n\t\t\t apidly divides and forms three distinct layers: the ectoderm
        \n\t\t\t (forms skin, hair, and nervous system), endoderm (forms
        \n\t\t\t digestive and respiratory systems), and mesoderm (forms
        \n\t\t\t muscles, bones, blood vessels, and other organs).
        \n\t\t• Primitive streak formation: A line of cells appears within the
        \n\t\t\t inner cell mass, called the primitive streak, which will
        \n\t\t\t eventually develop into the baby\'s nervous system.

        \n\t\t• Yolk sac development: A small sac outside the embryo, called
        \n\t\t\t the yolk sac, provides early nourishment until the placenta
        \n\t\t\t takes over.

        \n\t\t• Amniotic sac development: A fluid-filled sac forms around \n\t\t\t the
        embryo, creating a protective environment.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Implantation bleeding: Some women may still experience \n\t\t\tlight
        spotting or bleeding.
        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may continue to feel
        \n\t\t\t swollen and tender, and nipples may become darker.
        \n\t\t• Fatigue: Feeling unusually tired is common due to hormonal
        \n\t\t\t changes and increased energy demands.
        \n\t\t• Nausea and vomiting: Morning sickness (which can occur at
        \n\t\t\t any time of day) may start affecting some women.
        \n\t\t• Food cravings or aversions: Changes in taste and smell can
        \n\t\t\t lead to specific cravings or aversions.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
        \n\t\t\t feel anything yet.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintain taking your prenatal
        \n\t\t\t vitamin for essential nutrients.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, regular exercise,
        \n\t\t\t and proper hydration.
        \n\t\t•Schedule prenatal appointment: If you haven\'t already, book
        \n\t\t\t a prenatal appointment with your doctor for early pregnancy
        \n\t\t\t check-ups and guidance.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Weight gain: Minimal weight gain, if any, is expected at this
        \n\t\t\t stage.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: Likely remains elevated if you\'ve
        \n\t\t\t been tracking it.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thicker and stickier as your \n\t\t\t body
        prepares for continued pregnancy.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions.





    </string>

    <string name="week5">
        \n Your baby resembles a tadpole more than a human, but is
        \n growing fast. The circulatory system is beginning to form, and
        \n cells in the tiny
        "heart"
        will start to flicker this week.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a sesame seed.\n\n

        Here\'s what happens during the 5th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Embryo growth: The embryo grows rapidly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a sesame seed.
        \n\t\t• Neural tube formation: The neural tube forms, which will
         \n\t\t\t eventually become the brain and spinal cord.
        \n\t\t• Heart development: The tiny heart starts beating, although
        \n\t\t\t it\'s still a simple tube structure.
        \n\t\t• Blood vessel development: The first blood vessels form,
        \n\t\t\t connecting the embryo to the developing placenta.
        \n\t\t• Placenta development: The placenta continues to grow and
        \n\t\t\t take over nourishing the embryo.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: Nausea and vomiting are common,
        \n\t\t\t although not everyone experiences them.
        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may continue to feel
        \n\t\t\t swollen and tender, and nipples may darken.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: You might need to urinate more often
        \n\t\t\t due to increased blood volume and pressure on the bladder.
        \n\t\t• Food cravings or aversions: Changes in taste and smell can
        \n\t\t\t  lead to specific preferences or dislikes.
        \n\t\t• Bloating: Increased progesterone levels can cause bloating.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Not everyone experiences pregnancy
        \n\t\t\t symptoms, and some might not feel anything yet.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintain taking your prenatal
        \n\t\t\t vitamin for essential nutrients.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointment: If you haven\'t already, book
        \n\t\t\t a prenatal appointment with your doctor for early
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy check-ups and guidance.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, regular exercise,
        \n\t\t\t and proper hydration.\n\n


        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Weight gain: Minimal weight gain, if any, is expected at this
        \n\t\t\t stage.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature:  No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy after ovulation.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thicker and stickier to support \n\t\t\t pregnancy.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions.
    </string>


    <string name="week6">
        Your baby\'s nose, mouth and ears are starting to take shape, and
        their intestines and brain are beginning to develop.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a lentil.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 6th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Rapid growth: The embryo, now called a fetus, nearly
        \n\t\t\tdoubles in size, reaching about the size of a lentil.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Tiny bumps appear where the eyes, nose,
        \n\t\t\tand ears will eventually form.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Tiny buds form, which will develop into
        \n\t\t\tarms and legs.
        \n\t\t• Internal organ development: The heart continues to beat, \n\t\t\tand
        the beginnings of the brain, lungs, and digestive system
        \n\t\t\tappear.
        \n\t\t• Placenta function: The placenta starts transferring nutrients
        \n\t\t\tand oxygen to the fetus and removing waste products.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: This is still common, and it can affect
        \n\t\t\twomen differently.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
        \n\t\t\tvolume and pressure on the bladder.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Hormonal changes can cause emotional
        \n\t\t\tfluctuations.
        \n\t\t• Bloating: Increased progesterone levels can still cause \n\t\t\tbloating.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Not everyone experiences pregnancy
        \n\t\t\tsymptoms, and some might not feel anything yet.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintain taking your prenatal
        \n\t\t\t vitamin for essential nutrients.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointment: If you haven\'t already, book
        \n\t\t\t a prenatal appointment with your doctor for early
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy check-ups and guidance.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, regular exercise,
        \n\t\t\t(with doctor\'s approval), and proper hydration.\n\n

         Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Weight gain: Minimal weight gain, if any, is expected at this
        \n\t\t\t stage.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature:  Not relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy anymore.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May become thicker and stickier to support \n\t\t\t pregnancy.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions.

    </string>

    <string name="week7">
        Your baby has doubled in size since last week, but still has a tail,
        which will soon disappear. Little hands and feet that look more
        like paddles are emerging from the developing arms and legs.
        \n\nYour baby is the size of a blueberry.
        \n\nHere\'s what happens during the 7th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth spurt: The fetus grows rapidly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a blueberry.
        \n\t\t• Facial structure: The facial features become more defined,
        \n\t\t\t with eyes forming eyelids and nostrils appearing.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Arm and leg buds become more distinct,
        \n\t\t\t with fingers and toes starting to develop.
        \n\t\t• Organ development: The brain, lungs, digestive system, and
        \n\t\t\t other organs continue to develop and become more \n\t\t\t complex.
        \n\t\t• Nervous system development: The nervous system matures,
        \n\t\t\t allowing for basic movements and reflexes.
        \n\t\t• Circulatory system development: The heart beats strong and
        \n\t\t\t pumps blood throughout the developing body.\n\n
        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: This can continue for some women, though
        \n\t\t\t it might start to improve for others.
        \n\t\t• Fatigue: Tiredness remains common due to hormonal
        \n\t\t\t  changes and increased energy demands.
       \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may continue to feel
        \n\t\t\t swollen and tender, and nipples may become darker and
        \n\t\t\t larger.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite: As your body nourishes the growing\n\t\t\t fetus,
        \n\t\t\t you might feel hungrier more often.
        \n\t\t• Food cravings or aversions: Changes in taste and smell can
        \n\t\t\t  still occur.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
        \n\t\t\t  volume and pressure on the bladder.
        \n\t\t• Bloating: Progesterone levels can still cause bloating.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Hormonal fluctuations can lead to emotional
        \n\t\t\t  ups and downs.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Not everyone experiences pregnancy
        \n\t\t\t symptoms in the same way, and some might not feel \n\t\t\t  anything yet.\n\n
        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: It\'s crucial to keep taking your
        \n\t\t\t prenatal vitamin for essential nutrients.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Attend regular check-ups
        \n\t\t\t with your doctor to monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t development.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Maintain a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider genetic testing: Discuss with your doctor if you
        \n\t\t\t have any concerns or risk factors for genetic conditions and
        \n\t\t\t whether genetic testing is right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Slight weight gain: You might start noticing a subtle increase
        \n\t\t\t in weight as your body nourishes the fetus.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Possible visible changes: Your clothes might start to feel a bit
        \n\t\t\t snugger around your abdomen, but a noticeable baby bump
        \n\t\t\t is unlikely at this stage.\n\n

        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.


    </string>
    <string name="week9">
        Your baby\'s basic anatomy is developing (they even have tiny earlobes now), but there\'s much more to come.
        Their embryonic
        tail has disappeared and they weigh just a fraction of an ounce
        but are about to start gaining weight fast.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a grape.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 9th week:\n

        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The fetus grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a grape.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to become more
        \n\t\t\t detailed, with eyelids opening and closing, and the
        \n\t\t\t beginnings of teeth forming.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed, with
        \n\t\t\t tiny nails visible. Muscles and bones develop further,
        \n\t\t\t allowing for more complex movements.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Internal organs continue to mature rapidly,
        \n\t\t\t with the brain showing significant development and the
        \n\t\t\t digestive system becoming more functional.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals develop more externally, and
        \n\t\t\t in some cases, the baby\'s sex may be discernible through
        \n\t\t\t ultrasound.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: For some women, this may start to improve
        \n\t\t\t or lessen in intensity.
        \n\t\t• Fatigue: While still common, fatigue might decrease as your
        \n\t\t\t body adjusts to hormonal changes.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite and food cravings/aversions: Your body
        \n\t\t\t needs more fuel for growth, leading to increased hunger
        \n\t\t\t and potential changes in taste and smell.
        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may still feel swollen
        \n\t\t\t and tender, but the tenderness typically starts to decrease.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
        \n\t\t\t volume and pressure on the bladder.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Hormonal fluctuations can still cause
        \n\t\t\t emotional ups and downs, but hopefully less intense than
        \n\t\t\t before.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You might start noticing a slight bump
        \n\t\t\t around your lower abdomen, although it\'s not yet a true
        \n\t\t\t baby bump.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
        \n\t\t\t feel anything yet.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintaining your prenatal vitamin
        \n\t\t\t intake is crucial for continued development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\t your doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t progress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t adequately hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor
        \n\t\t\t whether prenatal screening tests like ultrasound or genetic
        \n\t\t\t testing are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Gradual weight gain: You might notice a steady increase in
        \n\t\t\t weight as your body nourishes the growing fetus.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Possible visible changes: A slight bump around your lower
        \n\t\t\t abdomen might be noticeable, but a prominent baby bump
        \n\t\t\t  is still not typical.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>
    <string name="week8">
        Your baby has started moving around, though you won\'t feel your
        baby move yet. Nerve cells are branching out, forming primitive
        neural pathways. Breathing tubes now extend from their throat to
        their developing lungs.\n\n

        Your baby is the size of a kidney bean.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 8th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The fetus grows dramatically, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t  the size of a kidney bean.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to become more
        \n\t\t\t  defined, with eyelids closing completely for a short period
        \n\t\t\t  and the nose becoming more prominent.
        \n\t\t•Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed, with
        \n\t\t\t  tiny nails starting to appear.
        \n\t\t• Muscle and bone development: Muscles and bones start to
        \n\t\t\t  develop, allowing for basic movements like flexing and
        \n\t\t\t kicking.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Internal organs continue to mature, with the
        \n\t\t\t  brain showing significant development and the digestive
        \n\t\t\t system becoming more functional
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals begin to develop externally,
        \n\t\t\t although it\'s still too early to determine the baby\'s sex.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: This might start to improve for some
        \n\t\t\t women, while others might continue to experience it.
        \n\t\t• Fatigue: Tiredness remains common due to hormonal
        \n\t\t\t changes and increased energy demands.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite and food cravings/aversions: Your body
       \n\t\t\t needs more fuel for growth, leading to increased hunger
         \n\t\t\t and potential changes in taste and smell.
        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may continue to feel
         \n\t\t\t swollen and tender, with nipples becoming darker and  \n\t\t\t larger.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
         \n\t\t\t volume and pressure on the bladder.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Hormonal fluctuations can still cause
        \n\t\t\t emotional ups and downs.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You might start noticing subtle changes in
         \n\t\t\t your body shape, but a pronounced baby bump is unlikely
         \n\t\t\t yet.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
         \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
         \n\t\t\t feel anything yet.

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintaining your prenatal vitamin
        \n\t\t\t intake is crucial for continued development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\t your doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t progress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t adequately hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor
        \n\t\t\t whether prenatal screening tests like ultrasound or genetic
        \n\t\t\t testing are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Slight weight gain: You might start noticing a subtle increase
        \n\t\t\t in weight as your body nourishes the fetus.
        \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
        \n\t\t• Possible visible changes: Clothes might feel a bit snugger,
        \n\t\t\t but a prominent baby bump is still not typical.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>
    <string name="week10">
        Your embryo has completed the most critical portion of
        development. Their skin is still translucent, but their tiny limbs can
        bend and fine details like nails are starting to form.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a kumquat.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 10th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The fetus grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a kumquat.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to refine, with the
        \n\t\t\t nose becoming more prominent and the lips forming.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed with
        \n\t\t\t tiny fingernails and toenails. Muscles and bones develop
        \n\t\t\tfurther, allowing for more complex movements like kicking
        \n\t\t\tand flexing.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Internal organs continue to mature rapidly,
        \n\t\t\t with the brain showing complex activity and the digestive
        \n\t\t\t system becoming even more functional.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\t baby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\t desired.\n\n
        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: This tends to improve significantly for most
        \n\t\t\t women by this week, although some may still experience
        \n\t\t\t nausea or vomiting occasionally.
        \n\t\t• Increased energy: As your body adjusts to hormonal
        \n\t\t\t changes, you may feel more energetic than in previous
        \n\t\t\tweeks.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite and food cravings/aversions: Your body
        \n\t\t\t still needs more fuel, but cravings may become less intense
       \n\t\t\t or even disappear.
        \n\t\t• Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may still feel slightly
        \n\t\t\t tender, but the discomfort should be significantly reduced.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
        \n\t\t\t volume and pressure on the bladder, but might become less
        \n\t\t\t frequent than before.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations can still occur, but
        \n\t\t\t hopefully less intense and frequent than earlier weeks.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: You might start noticing a more defined
        \n\t\t\t bump around your lower abdomen, marking the beginning
        \n\t\t\t of your visible baby bump.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
        \n\t\t\t feel anything noticeable.\n\n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintaining your prenatal vitamin
        \n\t\t\t intake is crucial for continued development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\t your doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t progress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t adequately hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor
        \n\t\t\t whether prenatal screening tests like ultrasound or genetic
        \n\t\t\t testing are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Steady weight gain: You might notice a steady increase in
        \n\t\t\t weight as your body nourishes the growing fetus.
         \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
         \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
       \n\t\t\t  pregnancy, but becoming less so gradually.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: A more defined bump around your lower
        \n\t\t\t abdomen is likely, marking the start of your visible baby bump.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="week11">
        Your baby is almost fully formed. They\'re kicking, stretching, and
        even hiccupping as their diaphragm develops, although you can\'t
        feel any activity yet.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a fig.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 11th week:
        \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The fetus grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a fig.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to refine, with
        \n\t\t\t distinct human characteristics like eyelids, lips, and a tiny
        \n\t\t\t nose becoming more prominent.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed with
        \n\t\t\t tiny fingernails and toenails, and the baby might start
        \n\t\t\t flexing and stretching limbs.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Internal organs continue to mature rapidly,
        \n\t\t\t with the brain showing complex activity, the digestive
        \n\t\t\t system becoming more functional, and the kidneys starting
        \n\t\t\t to produce urine.
        \n\t\t• Skeletal development: Bones become harder and more
        \n\t\t\t developed, allowing for more coordinated movements.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\t baby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\t desired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Morning sickness: This should significantly improve for most
        \n\t\t\t women, although occasional nausea or vomiting might still
        \n\t\t\t occur.
        \n\t\t• Increased energy: You might feel more energetic than in
        \n\t\t\t previous weeks as your body adjusts to hormonal changes.
        \n\t\t\tIncreased appetite and food cravings/aversions: Your body
        \n\t\t\t still needs more fuel, but cravings may become less intense
        \n\t\t\t or even disappear.
        \n\t\t•Breast tenderness and changes: Breasts may still feel slightly
        \n\t\t\t tender, but the discomfort should be significantly reduced.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: This continues due to increased blood
        \n\t\t\t volume and pressure on the bladder, but might become less
        \n\t\t\t frequent than before.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations can still occur, but
        \n\t\t\t hopefully less intense and frequent than earlier weeks.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more noticeable
        \n\t\t\t and defined, and some women might start experiencing skin
        \n\t\t\t changes like a pregnancy glow.
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
        \n\t\t\tfeel anything noticeable.\n \n

        Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintaining your prenatal vitamin
        \n\t\t\t intake is crucial for continued development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\t your doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t progress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t adequately hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor
        \n\t\t\t whether prenatal screening tests like ultrasound or genetic
        \n\t\t\t testing are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Steady weight gain: You might notice a steady increase in
        \n\t\t\t weight as your body nourishes the growing fetus.
         \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
         \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
       \n\t\t\t  pregnancy, but becoming less so gradually.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: A more defined bump around your lower
        \n\t\t\t abdomen is likely, marking the start of your visible baby
        \n\t\t\t bump.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.

    </string>


    <string name="week12">
        This week your baby\'s reflexes kick in: Their fingers will soon begin
        to open and close, toes will curl, and their mouth will make
        sucking movements.\n\n
        Your baby is the size of a lime.\n\n
        Here\'s what happens during the 12th week:\n
        \n\t\t• Entering the second trimester: This week marks the exciting
        \n\t\t\t transition into the second trimester, which is often referred
        \n\t\t\t to as the "honeymoon phase" due to decreased nausea and
        \n\t\t\t increased energy levels for many women.
       \n\t\t• Fetal growth: The fetus grows significantly, reaching about
        \n\t\t\t the size of a lime.
        \n\t\t• Facial features: Facial features continue to develop with
        \n\t\t\t distinct characteristics becoming more recognizable,
        \n\t\t\t including eyebrows, eyelids, and a more defined nose.
        \n\t\t• Limb development: Fingers and toes are fully formed with
        \n\t\t\t tiny fingernails and toenails, and the baby might start
        \n\t\t\t grasping, sucking their thumb, and making more
        \n\t\t\t coordinated movements.
        \n\t\t• Internal organs: Internal organs continue to mature rapidly,
        \n\t\t\t with the brain showing complex activity, the digestive
        \n\t\t\t system absorbing nutrients from swallowed amniotic fluid,
        \n\t\t\t and the kidneys functioning more efficiently.
        \n\t\t• Skeletal development: Bones become stronger and more
        \n\t\t\t developed, allowing for more coordinated movements and
        \n\t\t\t muscle development.
        \n\t\t• Genital development: Genitals are fully formed, and the
        \n\t\t\t baby\'s sex is usually determinable through ultrasound if
        \n\t\t\t desired.\n\n

        Possible signs and symptoms:
        \n\t\t• Reduced morning sickness: For most women, the dreaded
        \n\t\t\t morning sickness should significantly improve or disappear
        \n\t\t\t altogether by this week.
        \n\t\t• Increased energy: You might feel more energetic and vibrant
        \n\t\t\t as hormonal changes stabilize and nausea subsides.
        \n\t\t• Increased appetite: Your body needs more fuel for the
        \n\t\t\t growing baby, so you might feel hungrier more often.
        \n\t\t• Food cravings/aversions: While still possible, these
        \n\t\t\t  tendencies
        \n\t\t\t often become less intense or disappear entirely.
        \n\t\t• Reduced breast tenderness: The discomfort in your breasts
        \n\t\t\t should be significantly reduced by now.
        \n\t\t• Frequent urination: You might still need to urinate more often
        \n\t\t\t due to increased blood volume and pressure on the bladder,
        \n\t\t\t but less frequently than earlier weeks.
        \n\t\t• Mood swings: Emotional fluctuations might still occur, but
        \n\t\t\t hopefully less intense and frequent than in the first
        \n\t\t\t trimester.
        \n\t\t•Visible changes: Your baby bump becomes more noticeable
        \n\t\t\t and defined, and some women might start experiencing skin
        \n\t\t\t changes like a"pregnancy glow" or linea nigra (a dark line
        \n\t\t\t down the abdomen).
        \n\t\t• No symptoms: Remember, not everyone experiences
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy symptoms in the same way, and some might not
        \n\t\t\t feel anything noticeable.\n\n

         Health interventions:
        \n\t\t• Continue prenatal vitamin: Maintaining your prenatal vitamin
        \n\t\t\t intake is crucial for continued development.
        \n\t\t• Schedule prenatal appointments: Regular check-ups with
        \n\t\t\t your doctor help monitor your health and the baby\'s
        \n\t\t\t progress.
        \n\t\t• Healthy lifestyle: Prioritize a balanced diet, engage in
        \n\t\t\t moderate exercise (approved by your doctor), and stay
        \n\t\t\t adequately hydrated.
        \n\t\t• Consider prenatal screening: Discuss with your doctor
        \n\t\t\t whether prenatal screening tests like ultrasound or genetic
        \n\t\t\t testing are right for you.\n\n

        Expectations for your body:
        \n\t\t• Steady weight gain: You might notice a steady increase in
        \n\t\t\t weight as your body nourishes the growing fetus.
         \n\t\t• Basal body temperature: No longer relevant for tracking
        \n\t\t\t pregnancy.
         \n\t\t• Cervical mucus: May remain thick and sticky to support
       \n\t\t\t  pregnancy, but becoming less so gradually.
        \n\t\t• Visible changes: A more defined bump around your lower
        \n\t\t\t abdomen is likely, marking the start of your visible baby
        \n\t\t\t bump.\n\n
        Remember:
        \n\t\t• Every pregnancy is unique, and these are general guidelines.
        \n\t\t• Consult your doctor with any concerns or questions you have
        \n\t\t\t about your pregnancy health and well-being.
    </string>

</resources>